txt. You're about to
do something very enjoyable,
which is to relax before sleeping.
Maybe in the world soon.
Relaxing before sleep.
Moment.
The human body.
The machine was.
Hinds away, goes mad and dies exhausted.
Whose life?
The moment the word goes out
but never.
A single.
Which so to speak.
The atmosphere of our brains like clouds.
Overlaid.
Her lower, lower, lower.
Animals
to their needs,
to their pleasures of life,
which they enjoy more than way
there are more apparent,
should not be as keen as ours,
because we are not
in the same state of necessity as they
let us observe man
both in and out of his shell.
Let us examine young embryos of four, six,
eight, 15 days with the microscope.
After that time, our eyes are sufficient.
What do we see?
I don't know, a little round egg
with two black banks to mark the eyes.
For that everything is formless.
And one sees only a book,
which is the brain and which are formed
the first roots, the nerves.
That is the principle of feeling
and the heart.
Jewelry within the substance
as the power of eating of itself.
And little by little
one sees the had lengthen from the neck,
which in dilating forms, for inside
which the heart has already sunk there
to become stationary
robot, is abdomen,
which is divided by a partition diaphragm.
One of these enlargements
of the body forms the arms of the hands,
the fingers, the nails and the hair.
The other forms of thighs.
The legs defeat et cetera, which differ
only in their observed situation
and which constitute
the support in the balancing body.
Whole process, is a strange
sort of growth, like that of a plant.
On the
tops of our heads is hair in place
of which the plants have leaves
and flowers everywhere,
as shown with the luxury of nature.
And finally, the directing principle
of plants is place where we have our soul.
That other quality of.
Thank you.